<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Australia Post - Update on your Australia Post enquiry Case: {!Case.CaseNumber}</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>BCP - Email on Day 3 - 25 May (Digital Enquiries 2.0)</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Australia Post - Update on your Australia Post enquiry Case: {!Case.CaseNumber}</subject>
    <textOnly>Australia Post

Help &amp; Support

Reference number {!Case.CaseNumber}


Dear {!Contact.FirstName},


Thank you for your enquiry on {!Case.CreatedDate} and we apologise for the delay in getting back to you.

We’re currently experiencing a high number of enquiries relating to delivery delays. These delays are due to limited flights, social distancing requirements and an increase in parcel volumes as more people shop online. Rest assured that we’re working hard to get your parcel to you as quickly as possible. We will be in touch with some more information as soon as we can.

In the meantime, you can continue checking the status of your delivery using our tracking tool, and keep up-to-date on any impacts and delays on our  important updates page.

If you have already received your parcel and no longer require assistance, please respond to this email and we can close your enquiry.

Thank you again for your support and patience during this time.

Your team at Australia Post.



Kind regards,
Australia Post
{!Case.Thread_Id}

Nothing in this email is intended to exclude or limit any rights or remedies that you may have under the Australian Consumer Law.

This email was sent by Australia Post. Australia Post does not represent, warrant or guarantee that the integrity of this email communication has been maintained nor that the communication is free of errors, viruses or interference.
Help &amp; support  |  Terms &amp; conditions  |  Privacy policy</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
