<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Email after custom has finished compensation form</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>SSSW Compensation Form Submitted Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>We&apos;ve received your payment details - Do Not Reply</subject>
    <textOnly>Australia Post 

We&apos;ve received your payment details

Hi {!Compensation__c.ContactFirstName__c},


Thanks for providing your payment details for case number: {!Compensation__c.Case_Number__c}

We&apos;re sending compensation for the value of {!Compensation__c.Total_Compensation_Amount__c}.

We&apos;re sending compensation for the value of {!Compensation__c.Total_Compensation_Amount__c} for your item with tracking number {!Compensation__c.Tracking_Number__c}.

What happens from here?

We&apos;ll process the compensation payment. Once the process is complete, we&apos;ll close your enquiry.

You&apos;ll receive the payment within 5 business days, depending on the destination bank&apos;s processing times.

If this compensation is for a late or missing item, it&apos;s possible that your item may still show up. If the item gets delivered after the compensation has been paid, it can be kept. No need to pay us back or open another case.

This email has been auto generated by an unmanned inbox, if additional assistance is required, please respond to the original e-mail thread with your Australia Post representative.

Thanks,
AusPost Customer Services




Australia Post will never send you an unsolicited email asking for your password, credit card details or account information


Terms &amp; conditions    Help &amp; support    Privacy policy

Nothing in this email is intended to exclude or limit any rights or remedies that you may have under the Australian Consumer Law.

This email was sent by Australia Post, 111 Bourke Street, MELBOURNE VIC 3000. If you have any concerns, or don&apos;t think you should have received this email, please call us on 13 13 18. Visit auspost.com.au for further information on our online security.

Australia Post does not represent, warrant or guarantee that the integrity of this email communication has been maintained nor that the communication is free from errors, viruses, or inteference.

@ 2020 Australia Post. All Rights Reserved.

Connect with Australia Post



Australia Post acknowledges the Traditional Custodians of the land on which we operate, live and gather as employees, and recognize their continuing connection to land, water and community. We pay respect to Elders past, present and emerging.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
