<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Credit Approval Request</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Approval Request for Case {!Credit_Approval__c.Case__c} - {!Credit_Approval__c.Billing_Account__c} - {!Credit_Approval__c.CreditAmountExclusiveGST__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>StartTrack

Approval Request

Dear Delegated Approver,

Please review the following credit claim and approve/reject this request within 2 business days to ensure a timely resolution can be achieved for our customer.

Case Details
Case type: {!Credit_Approval__c.Case_Type__c}
Case number: {!Credit_Approval__c.Case__c}
Billing Account Name: {!Credit_Approval__c.Billing_Account__c}
Product family: {!Credit_Approval__c.Product_Family__c}
Sub-product: {!Credit_Approval__c.Product_Sub_Category__c}
Total proposed credit: {!Credit_Approval__c.CreditAmountExclusiveGST__c}
Proposed credit requiring your approval: {!Credit_Approval__c.Total_Claim_Amount__c}  (this amount will only be different if claim relates to multiple product families)
Case summary:
{!Credit_Approval__c.Case_Summary__c}

Click here to view the full credit claim details in Salesforce.

Please approve/reject this credit claim by clicking on the link provided above or replying to this email with the words &quot;Approve&quot; or &quot;Reject&quot; in the first line of the email message.

If replying via email, you can also add comments on the second line or otherwise add comments directly into the case whilst in Salesforce.

For any questions about this credit claim, please contact the Customer Resolution Team via the email provided below.


Regards,
Customer Resolution Team
Australia Post &amp; StarTrack
customer.resolutions@auspost.com.au


Australia Post will never send you an email asking for your password, credit card details or account information.


This email was sent by Australia Post, 									  111 Bourke Street, MELBOURNE VIC 3000. If you have any concerns, or don&apos;t think you should have received this email, 									  please call us on 13 13 18. 									  Visit auspost.com.au for further information on our online security.

Australia Post does not represent, warrant or guarantee that the integrity of this email communication has been maintained nor that the communication is free from errors, viruses, or interference.

Help &amp; Support | Terms &amp; Conditions | Privacy Policy</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
