<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>SSSW - Used to notify the customer that the case has been closed automatically by the system if there are no exceptions</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>SSSW Case Exception Checker Closure</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Missing parcel enquiry update</subject>
    <textOnly>Australia Post

Help &amp; 										Support


Hi {!Contact.FirstName},

Thanks for your patience while we’ve conducted our investigation for your 											missing parcel.

Case 													Number:  {!Case.CaseNumber}

Tracking 													Number:  {!Case.ReferenceID__c}

We’ve checked our delivery network and found no further updates for your 											parcel. 											It hasn’t been logged at our Returned Mail Redistribution Centre, where we 											store undeliverable 											items and loose contents.

We regret to advise that despite our investigation, we haven’t been able to 											locate your parcel. 											With all possible checks completed, your parcel is now considered lost.

We had hoped to give you a happier outcome today, and we’re sorry that we 											couldn’t.

What to do next

Please contact the sender of your parcel. Let them know your parcel is lost 											and ask for assistance with your 											order. You can share this email with them as confirmation of your lost 											parcel.

You should contact the sender because they are best placed to offer you a 											solution according to their policies. If the 											sender can’t assist you, please let us know.

We sincerely apologise for any disappointment or inconvenience this may have 											caused you.

Kind regards,
Customer Services
Australia Post


Nothing in this email is intended to exclude or limit any rights or remedies that you 							may have under the Australian Consumer Law. For more information, 							visit compensation

Australia Post acknowledges the Traditional Custodians of the land on which we operate, 							live and gather as employees and recognise their continuing connection to land, water and 							community. We pay respect to Elders past, present and emerging.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
