<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>For senders to waive entitlements in favour of addressees.</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Waiver of Entitlement</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Australia Post - Case: {!Case.CaseNumber}.</subject>
    <textOnly>Australia Post

Help &amp; Support

Reference {!Case.CaseNumber}

We’re sorry that we couldn’t find your missing parcel and would like to compensate you for the loss.

Usually when a parcel goes missing, the sender is entitled to claim, however with your authorisation, we can issue compensation to the addressee.


What do I need to do?

Print the email and complete the below form
Sign the declaration
Scan and send to us by replying to this email.

What if I don’t have a scanner?

If you are unable to send your waiver to us via reply email you can send it via mail to:

Australia Post
Customer Contact Centre
GPO Box 9911
Melbourne VIC 3001

Please note that claims sent via mail may take longer as we need to allow processing time.

What happens next?

We will issue a Money Order to the addressee which will be sent to the below address via mail.

Waiver of compensation form

Parcel details
Tracking number  ________________________________________________________________
Reference number  ________________________________________________________________
Addressee details
Full name  ______________________________________________________________________
Details

Street_____________________________________________________________________________

Suburb______________________________
State________________
Postcode______________

Country______________________________  Phone number   (______)_______________________

Your details
Full name  ______________________________________________________________________
Details

Street_____________________________________________________________________________

Suburb______________________________
State________________
Postcode______________

Country______________________________  Phone number   (______)_______________________

Sender acknowledgement
I acknowledge that by signing and returning this form to Australia Post, I am:

Consenting to the unconditional and irrevocable assignment of my right to claim compensation in relation to the abovementioned article to the addressee; and
Authorising Australia Post to carry out the assignment upon receipt of this application.


Signature: ________________________ Date: ____/____/____

Need help or have another enquiry?

Please visit Help &amp; Support to:

contact our support team directly
find answers to many commonly asked questions


Regards,
{!User.FirstName} {!LEFT(User.LastName,1)}
Australia Post
{!Case.Thread_Id}



Nothing in this email is intended to exclude or limit any rights or remedies that you may have under the Australian Consumer Law.

This email was sent by Australia Post. Australia Post does not represent, warrant or guarantee that the integrity of this email communication has been maintained nor that the communication is free of errors, viruses or interference.
Help &amp; support  |  Terms &amp; conditions  |  Privacy policy</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
