<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>2014-09 APMS</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>SOP Acknowledgment Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>SecurePay Online Payments application submitted – {!Application__c.Name}</subject>
    <textOnly>Hi {!Application__c.ContactFirstName__c},

Thank you for choosing SecurePay, a business of Australia Post, as your online payments partner.

We’ve received your application for a SecurePay Online Payments account and your application number is {!Application__c.Name}. You can quote this number if you have any questions about your application status.

SecurePay Online Payments details and pricing
You’ve applied for a SecurePay Online Payments account, which will allow you to accept secure online payments. This includes an internet merchant account to process the payments and a payment gateway to securely link your e-commerce website to your internet merchant account.

A SecurePay Online Payments account has:
• a 2.4 per cent fee on domestic Visa and MasterCard transactions, deducted when a payment is processed
• no additional transaction fees
• no set-up fees, no monthly or annual fees, and no long-term contracts.

Next steps
Please email a copy of your business bank account statement to {!$Setup.APMSSetting__c.SopEmailTemplateEmail__c}. This can be in the form of PDF or image. Please ensure your application number is included in the subject line.

We’ll be in touch within three business days to let you know the status of your application.

In the meantime, if you need more details about SecurePay Online Payments or you’d like to check on your application, you can call {!$Setup.APMSSetting__c.AusPostSupportPhone__c} (option 1) or email: {!$Setup.APMSSetting__c.SopEmailTemplateEmail__c}

If you need any assistance, please let us know – we’re here to help.

Regards,

The SecurePay Online Payments Team
SecurePay Pty Ltd – a business of Australia Post

W {!$Setup.APMSSetting__c.SopEmailTemplateWebsite__c}
P {!$Setup.APMSSetting__c.AusPostSupportPhone__c}
E {!$Setup.APMSSetting__c.SopEmailTemplateEmail__c}

Australia Post is committed to providing our customers with excellent service. If we can assist you in any way please telephone 13 13 18 or visit our website.

The information contained in this email communication may be proprietary, confidential or legally professionally privileged. It is intended exclusively for the individual or entity to which it is addressed. You should only read, disclose, re-transmit, copy, distribute, act in reliance on or commercialise the information if you are authorised to do so. Australia Post does not represent, warrant or guarantee that the integrity of this email communication has been maintained nor that the communication is free of errors, virus or interference.

If you are not the addressee or intended recipient please notify us by replying direct to the sender and then destroy any electronic or paper copy of this message. Any views expressed in this email communication are taken to be those of the individual sender, except where the sender specifically attributes those views to Australia Post and is authorised to do so.

Please consider the environment before printing this email.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
