<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Final reminder to use new forms: Existing CLMs 2nd email template</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>ExternalContactEmail</letterhead>
    <name>Form generator launch comms to Existing CLMs 2nd email template</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Final reminder to use new forms: VOI for Property Transfers in store service - {!Lead.FirstName}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Lead.FirstName},

New Verification of Identity forms now available

Today, we’re pleased to launch two new versions of the Verification of Identity (VOI) forms for property transfers that will be quicker and easier for you and your clients to complete.

Self-service online form generator

You have a choice of two V5.10 VOI forms that can now be accessed via the self-service online form generator links below.
1. Reusable version V5.10: pre-populated with your company name. Simply print this as required for your client to complete manually.
2. Single-use version V5.10: also pre-populated with your company name but allows you to complete it online with your client details.

To log into the online form generator, you will need:
1. your 5-digit number (CLMID) which is found next to your name above.
2. your passcode which has been set to the postcode of the business postal address you submitted to Australia Post during registration.

These customised forms display your company name and barcode, and determine where we electronically deliver each VOI Report.

We encourage you to start using these new and improved forms immediately, however you can continue to use the (V4.14) version of the VOI Form until 31 May, 2018.

Client Authorisation Form Training
We have recently completed upskill training for our Post Office retail staff. Our staff will now be prompted to ask your clients if they have a Client Authorisation Form (CAF) and will ensure these are compliant.

Need help?
Our team is here to help. If you’d like us to call you or to respond to a question via email, please reach out to us on landtitleVOI@auspost.com.au.

Kind regards,

The Australia Post Property Transfers VOI support team.
Both web-forms are hosted by Decipha Pty Ltd, a business of Australia Post.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
