<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>false</available>
    <description>Confirmation: VOI for Property Transfers in store service</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>ExternalContactEmail</letterhead>
    <name>OPFG Salesforce 2nd email template to new CLMs</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Confirmation: VOI for Property Transfers in store service - {!Lead.FirstName} {!Lead.LastName}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Lead.FirstName},

We are pleased to advise that you are now able to use the Australia Post Verification of Identity (VOI) in store service for Property Transfers, to have your clients’ identity verified by Australia Post at our participating post offices.



Self-service online form generator



You have a choice of two versions of the Verification of Identity (VOI) forms for property transfers that are quick and easy for you and your clients to complete and can be accessed via the self-service online form generator links below.


Reusable version V5.10: pre-populated with your company name. Simply print this as required for your client to complete manually.
Single-use version V5.10: also pre-populated with your company name but allows you to complete online with your client details.



To log into the online form generator, you will need:




your 5-digit number (CLMID) which is found next to your name above.
your passcode which has been set to the postcode of the business postal address you submitted to Australia Post during registration.



These customised forms display your company name and barcode, and determine where we electronically deliver each VOI Report.



Reports for all VOI checks completed by either yourself using the do it yourself VOI tool, or in store by Australia Post, are stored in the VOI Report Portal at https://ltdia.com.au. You can access the portal using your existing login details. For your reference, a copy of the instructions for the VOI Report Portal are also attached.



If you require any assistance please contact us via email LandTitleVOI@auspost.com.au or call us on 1300 364 543.



Kind regards,



Australia Post Property Transfers VOI team</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
