<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>VOI Tool for Property Transfers registration</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>ExternalContactEmail</letterhead>
    <name>OPFG Salesforce 1st email template to new CLMs</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>VOI Tool for Property Transfers registration - {!Lead.FirstName}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Lead.FirstName},

Thank you for completing the online registration form for Australia Post’s do it yourself Verification of Identity (VOI) Tool for Property Transfers.

We are pleased to advise that you are now able to use this tool to support you in verifying your clients’ identity.

Your login credentials are

Username -

Password -

You can access the tool at https://auspost.com.au/propertytransfer/#/login

Instructions on how to use the do it yourself VOI tool are available through the Help link available on the login page.

VOI in store at Australia Post

If you wish to also offer your clients to have their VOI check completed by us at our participating Australia Post post offices, please print, sign and return a copy of the attached VOI (Property Transfers) Referral Agreement: via email to: LandTitleVOI@auspost.com.au

Or via post to:

Property Transfers VOI

Reply Paid 4310

Once we have received your signed agreement we will send you your customised Property Transfers VOI form. The form needs to be presented by your clients at participating Post Offices (auspost.com.au/find/landtitle) in order for them to have their identity verified by Australia Post.

VOI Report Portal

Reports for VOI checks that you’ve completed yourself using the VOI tool, or by Australia Post staff in store, can be accessed in the VOI Report Portal.

The VOI Report Portal can be accessed through the dashboard of the VOI tool or directly at https://ltdia.com.au.  Instructions on how to use the VOI Report Portal, including how to change your password, are attached.

If you require any assistance please contact us via email LandTitleVOI@auspost.com.au or call us on 1300 364 543.



Kind regards,

Australia Post Property Transfers VOI team</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
